<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Jon's Site</title><link>https://joundy.me/</link><description>Recent content on Jon's Site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 22:54:04 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://joundy.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Blockchain: Deploy NFT Contract in Near Protocol</title><link>https://joundy.me/posts/blockchain-deploy-nft-contract-in-near-protocol/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 22:54:04 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://joundy.me/posts/blockchain-deploy-nft-contract-in-near-protocol/</guid><description>Intro Hello guys, I hope everyone is doing well, in this post I am going to create an NFT (Non-Fungible Token) contract in Near protocol, have you ever heard of near protocol? near protocol is a layer 1 blockchain network, like an Ethereum network, near uses Proof of Stake (POS) instead of Proof of Work (POW), besides of that the Near protocol has excellent features like Nightshade Sharding that can validate a transaction really fast, personally, I really enjoy developing Dapps in near rather than another blockchain, but because near is relatively new, there are very few tutorials out there, so this is one the reason why I created this article, by the way, you can learn more about near on this website near developer.</description></item><item><title>Concurrency and Parallelism</title><link>https://joundy.me/posts/concurrency-and-parallelism/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 21:39:57 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://joundy.me/posts/concurrency-and-parallelism/</guid><description>Intro Parallelism and concurrency are topics that make a lot of programmers confused, and some programmers can’t figure out the difference between them, personally, this topic is not beginner friendly, but it can be nice if you could understand it deeply, back then when I code some project I don’t consider how the process is processed behind the scene, I don’t know how to optimize some process to be more fast and efficient.</description></item><item><title>Jon's Resume</title><link>https://joundy.me/resume/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2022 22:54:04 +0700</pubDate><guid>https://joundy.me/resume/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>